[
 {"question":"Jaws Playground", "answer":"Shark Park", "hint":"Shark", "level": 4, "item":1, "completed": false, "id":61},
 {"question":"Large Branch", "answer":"Big Twig", "hint":"Big", "level": 4, "item":2, "completed": false, "id":62},
 {"question":"Turbulent Sauce", "answer":"Wavy Gravy", "hint":"Wavy", "level": 4, "item":3, "completed": false, "id":63},
 {"question":"Money Hoard", "answer":"Cash Stash", "hint":"Cash", "level": 4, "item":4, "completed": false, "id":64},
 {"question":"Long Snooze", "answer":"Deep Sleep", "hint":"Deep", "level": 4, "item":5, "completed": false, "id":65},
 {"question":"Thrifty Loser", "answer":"Cheap Creep", "hint":"Cheap", "level": 4, "item":6, "completed": false, "id":66},
 {"question":"Maroon Cradle", "answer":"Red Bed", "hint":"Red", "level": 4, "item":7, "completed": false, "id":67},
 {"question":"Desert Musicians", "answer":"Sand Band", "hint":"Sand", "level": 4, "item":8, "completed": false, "id":68},
 {"question":"Pacific Movement", "answer":"Ocean Motion", "hint":"Ocean", "level": 4, "item":9, "completed": false, "id":69},
 {"question":"Stupefying Firearm", "answer":"Stun Gun", "hint":"Stun", "level": 4, "item":10, "completed": false, "id":70},
 {"question":"Learning Friend", "answer":"Study Buddy", "hint":"Study", "level": 4, "item":11, "completed": false, "id":71},
 {"question":"Stockings Container", "answer":"Socks Box", "hint":"Socks", "level": 4, "item":12, "completed": false, "id":72},
 {"question":"Narcotic Hoodlum", "answer":"Drug Thug", "hint":"Drug", "level": 4, "item":13, "completed": false, "id":73},
 {"question":"Intoxicated Smelly Mammal", "answer":"Drunk Skunk", "hint":"Drunk", "level": 4, "item":14, "completed": false, "id":74},
 {"question":"Foolish Young Female Horse", "answer":"Silly Filly", "hint":"Silly", "level": 4, "item":15, "completed": false, "id":75},
 {"question":"Sound Mind", "answer":"Sane Brain", "hint":"Sane", "level": 4, "item":16, "completed": false, "id":76},
 {"question":"White Wood Temple", "answer":"Birch Church", "hint":"Birch", "level": 4, "item":17, "completed": false, "id":77},
 {"question":"Domestic Old Book", "answer":"Home Tome", "hint":"Home", "level": 4, "item":18, "completed": false, "id":78},
 {"question":"Thin Divider", "answer":"Fine Line", "hint":"Fine", "level": 4, "item":19, "completed": false, "id":79},
 {"question":"Sketched Baby Deer", "answer":"Drawn Fawn", "hint":"Drawn", "level": 4, "item":20, "completed": false, "id":60}
 
  ]